http://www.land-craft.com/privacy

L A N D C R A F T ' S Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is LandCraft Inc.'s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://www.land-craft.com, and other sites we own and operate.We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.This policy is effective as of 10 September 2018.
Copyright © 1978-2020 LandCraft, Inc.All Rights Reserved. Unauthorized Use of Pictures and Content is Prohibited.
List of ServicesBoat & Jet Ski RepairInsurance Claim HandlingMobile Marine ServicesBoat RestorationsFabricationsRV & Truck FiberglassIndustrial FiberglassServices Overview
PortfolioBoat Repair PicturesBoat Restoration PicturesFabrication PicturesRV & Truck Repair PicturesIndustrial Repair PicturesProject Spotlight PicturesMisc. Fiberglass PicturesPhoto Gallery
Other LinksFinancingSpecial OffersHelpful Boater ResourcesQuality GuidelinesFAQLocal MarinasFor SaleLandCraft Gear
Company InformationAbout UsContact Us / LocationCareer OpportunitiesNews & PressTestimonials
Join Email List
LandCraft Marine specializes in structural boat repairs to minor cosmetic fixes. Our services include fiberglass and gel coat repair, metal flake repair, aluminum boat repair, re-coring decks and hulls, rotted wood floor and transom replacement, hull painting, gel coat refurbishing, custom fabrication services, and total boat restorations and refits. Our services are available for recreational, commercial and industrial applications. LandCraft Marine serves the Chicago metropolitan area as well as surrounding Illinois suburbs: Alsip, Aurora, Barrington, Bolingbrook, Bourbonnais, Bradley, Bridgeview, Burr Ridge, Chicago, Chicago Ridge, Country Club Hills, Countryside, Crestwood, Downers Grove, Evergreen Park, Flossmoor, Fox Lake, Frankfort, Hazel Crest, Hinsdale, Homer Glen, Homewood, Joliet, Kankakee, La Grange, Lansing, Lemont, Lockport, Manteno, Matteson, Merrionette Park, Midlothian, Mokena, Monee, Morris, Naperville, New Lenox, Oak Brook, Oak Forest, Oak Lawn, Olympia Fields, Orland Hills, Orland Park, Palos Heights, Palos Hills, Palos Park, Peotone, Richton Park, Romeoville, Schaumburg, South Holland, Steger, Summit, Thornton, Tinley Park, University Park, Western Springs, Wheaton, Worth, & all other locales. We provide services throughout Illinois and NW Indiana, including Cook County, Will County, DuPage County, Kane County, Lake County and surrounding areas.
Privacy Policy  l  Terms"LandCraft" is a trademark of LandCraft Inc registered in the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office and may be registered in certain jurisdictions. Chicago Website Design
by SmallBee.com
Share by:
